<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Call of Cthulhu - Cosmic Horrors (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.CallofCthulhuCosmicHorrors</packageId>
  <author>Jecrell</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/CallofCthulhuCosmicHorrors</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
    <li>
      <packageId>jecrell.jecstools</packageId>
      <displayName>JecsTools</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2195729899</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
    <li>jecrell.jecstools</li>
    <li>CETeam.CombatExtended</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>Update of Jecrells mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=765890823

[img]https://i.imgur.com/GYswkZ7.png[/img]

Support-chat:
https://invite.gg/mlie

Non-steam version:
https://github.com/emipa606/CallofCthulhuCosmicHorrors

- This is an unofficial port
- This will be removed when/if Jecrell comes back
- Added support for Combat Extended based on Saebbis mod: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1357967363
	
--- Original Description ---
*Add Lovecraftian monsters to your RimWorld experience!* 
There is a lingering fear that strokes the hairs on the back of the necks of your colonists. Something terrible is coming, and there is little time to prepare. Cosmic horrors are already upon us.

Features:
This is an attempt to create the minor races of H.P. Lovecraft's weird fiction mythos in the RimWorld engine. Some behave the same as hostile factions that raid colonies such as mechanoids or insectoids. Others can be deadlier, however.

Adds the following cosmic horrors to your game:
Star-Spawn of Cthulhu
Shoggoths
Mi-Go
Deep Ones
Star Vampire
Dark Young
NEW Chthonian

!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
NOTICE
!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
You will need to start a new game OR for previously saved games without monsters, you can try using Orion's Faction Discovery Mod
*phew* Now that that's out of the way. Onto the notes section!


Notes:
Each monster has its own unique anatomical skeletons, organs, and body parts. Some special powers were given to psionic beasts.
Each monster has special sound effects.
More creatures will be added in a second update in the near future. A third update will flesh out these cosmic horrors with true special abilities true to their literary counterparts.
Since I am one person, I can't attest to how balanced the monsters are, and I am definitely looking for feedback from player experiences. Let me know how they are in your game.

Update 1.3
Dark Young and Dark Young Herd incidents added to the game.
Greater Deep Ones added to the game.
Star Vampires rebalanced to be more numerous at higher difficulties.
All cosmic horrors have age ranges from Spawn to Eldritch.
Sanity loss effects now apply when observing Cosmic Horrors.
Mood loss effects now apply when observing Cosmic Horrors.
Sanity Loss effects further rebalanced

Call of Cthulhu Mods
Introducing the H.P. Lovecraft Storyteller (Standard / Double Population)
Call of Cthulhu - Neutral Factions add secretive coastal fishing villages, The Agency, themed guns, hats, outfits, and more! Don't want the factions but just the items? We have the Items Only Edition, too.
Industrial Age Object Pack! Now you can add some early 20th century style to your colonies.
Want to play as cultists? Then the Call of Cthulhu Cults Gameplay Expansion Pack is for you.
Get some straitjackets to keep your colonists from going insane.
Want more? Check out the Call of Cthulhu WIP thread[ludeon.com] on the official RimWorld forums at Ludeon.
Recommended Mods
Colonists feeling nervous? There's Jecrell's Tobacco and Cigarettes

Credited Sources
Star Spawn of Cthulhu - ScribbleNauts[www.scribblenauts.com]
Shoggoth - Side Sprite - http://www.puppetnightmares.com/species-status/70/
MiGo - Side Sprite - Tatsuya Mottsuo[monsterbrains.blogspot.kr]
Deep Ones (My artwork)
Star Vampires (My artwork)
Sound Effects - Call of Cthulhu - Dark Corners of the Earth (PC)
Sound Effects - Dead Space (PC)
</description>
</ModMetaData>